{
    "subject": "resource/Bangalore_Nagarathnamma",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bangalore",
    "human_readable": "Bangalore Nagarathnamma was born in Bangalore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9219781160354614,
            "question": "Where was Nagarathnamma born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7811135649681091,
            "question": "Who is Nagarathnamma?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45954760909080505,
            "question": "Name a famous person from Bangalore."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3584690988063812,
            "question": "What is Bangalore known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26440903544425964,
            "question": "Is Bangalore a city in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23483918607234955,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Bangalore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15774381160736084,
            "question": "Is Bangalore a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13562025129795074,
            "question": "Does Bangalore have a rich cultural history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12785756587982178,
            "question": "What are some famous landmarks in Bangalore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1038338840007782,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Bangalore?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bangalore Nagarathnamma was born in Bangalore.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8701_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some famous landmarks in Bangalore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8701_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Bangalore have a rich cultural history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8701_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Bangalore a popular tourist destination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8701_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8701_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n**Triple:** Bangalore Nagarathnamma was born in Bangalore.\n\n**Evaluation:**\n\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided indicates that Bangalore Nagarathnamma was born in Nanjangud (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8701/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt), which is some fifteen kilometers from Mysore (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8701/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt). There is no mention of her being born in Bangalore."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information supporting that Bangalore Nagarathnamma was born in Bangalore. According to the provided context, she originally hailed from Nanjangud and later lived in Mysore and Bengaluru. There is no mention of her birthplace being specifically Bangalore."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}